[
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "javascript",
    "question": "What is a variable?",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "A container for storing data."
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "javascript",
    "question": "Write a function to output the numbers 0 through 5",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "for (let i = 0; i <= 5; i++) {\n console.log(i) \n}"
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "javascript",
    "question": "What is a function?",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "A block of code designed to perform a particular task which is executed when invoked."
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "javascript",
    "question": "What does the forEach method do?",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "It calls a function for each element in an array."
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "javascript",
    "question": "What is the key advantage of Object Oriented Programming?",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "Object Oriented Programming pairs data with functionality."
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "react",
    "question": "What is the key advantage of Object Oriented Programming?",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "Object Oriented Programming pairs data with functionality."
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "react",
    "question": "Create a functional component called Title which renders an h1 that says 'Hello'",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "const Title = () => { return <h1>Hello</h1> }"
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "express",
    "question": "Write a route handler for a GET request to the endpoint '/home'",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "app.get('/home', (req, res) => { res.status(200) } )"
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "express",
    "question": "Write a route handler for a POST request to the endpoint '/home'",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "app.post('/home', (req, res) => { res.status(200) } )"
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "redux",
    "question": "What do you need to wrap around your root App component to give it access to global state?",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "<Provider store={store}> <App /> </Provider>"
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "css",
    "question": "How can you horizontally and vertically center a div using flexbox?",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "div {display: flex; justify-content: center; align-items: center"
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "sql",
    "question": "Write a SQL query that grabs all rows from a table",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "SELECT * FROM table_name"
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "sql",
    "question": "Write a SQL query that grabs all rows from a table where the name is 'Anna'",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "SELECT * FROM table_name WHERE name=Anna"
  },
  {
    "userId": "",
    "category": "css",
    "question": "Style a button so that all of its default styling is removed",
    "description": "",
    "answer": "button { all: unset }"
  }
]
